{"data":[{"_id":"1110b140883291eca83f985c6d140cc2","_rev":"3-dfca008879ca0cf94c6391d69a1ed3fb","answer":"","answered":true,"answered_by":{"teacher_id":"th-1","teacher_name":"marry, john"},"answered_date":"2020-07-25","asked_by":{"student_id":"st-1","student_name":"will, smith"},"asked_date":"2020-07-12","question":"How many rivers are in Newyork?","viewed":false,"viewed_date":""},{"_id":"12b8085265e7d0f8be7c32c364228e1d","_rev":"13-3a1920709c964ad7309d363d4e86f4c9","answer":"River Colorado","answered":true,"answered_by":{"teacher_id":"th-1","teacher_name":"marry, john"},"answered_date":"2020-07-25","asked_by":{"student_id":"st-1","student_name":"will, smith"},"asked_date":"2020-6-26","question":"which is the longest river in USA?","viewed":true,"viewed_date":"2020-07-12"},{"_id":"2e63b6fd99b4437b9ede5e14cf67d0e2","_rev":"1-b19c95c96ec30bbbef97ee2f71dbf37e","answer":"","answered":false,"answered_by":{"teacher_id":"th-2","teacher_name":"willson, ng"},"answered_date":"","asked_by":{"student_id":"st-1","student_name":"will, smith"},"asked_date":"2020-07-17","question":"What is action?","viewed":false,"viewed_date":""},{"_id":"3e6d6d43008440d484ff028ef7c52735","_rev":"1-1ea92b057f20e3973a3b817c641c4cfe","answer":"","answered":false,"answered_by":{"teacher_id":"th-2","teacher_name":"willson, ng"},"answered_date":"","asked_by":{"student_id":"st-1","student_name":"will, smith"},"asked_date":"2020-07-18","question":"What are the 3 part of brain?","viewed":false,"viewed_date":""},{"_id":"48d46e273c7f182b35effe47fa836f2a","_rev":"1-2aa210c02d6459c99dfb60818065ff9e","answer":"","answered":false,"answered_by":{"teacher_id":"th-2","teacher_name":"willson, ng"},"answered_date":"","asked_by":{"student_id":"st-1","student_name":"will, smith"},"asked_date":"2020-07-18","question":"longest river in tamilnadu","viewed":false,"viewed_date":""},{"_id":"5380c942d229f2d11c1686fdfb6f4f06","_rev":"1-01eb05e4cdcf4129676f3564ef88bca3","answer":"","answered":false,"answered_by":{"teacher_id":"th-2","teacher_name":"willson, ng"},"answered_date":"","asked_by":{"student_id":"st-1","student_name":"will, smith"},"asked_date":"2020-07-17","question":"What is mass?","viewed":false,"viewed_date":""},{"_id":"6aecbba660090b398aab031e348ad2c4","_rev":"1-4a8fa0f34b786d84718dda6c9db92570","answer":"","answered":false,"answered_by":{"teacher_id":"th-2","teacher_name":"willson, ng"},"answered_date":"","asked_by":{"student_id":"st-1","student_name":"will, smith"},"asked_date":"2020-07-16","question":"What is force?","viewed":false,"viewed_date":""},{"_id":"82fb8d569371946369206c882cb32f88","_rev":"1-2aa210c02d6459c99dfb60818065ff9e","answer":"","answered":false,"answered_by":{"teacher_id":"th-2","teacher_name":"willson, ng"},"answered_date":"","asked_by":{"student_id":"st-1","student_name":"will, smith"},"asked_date":"2020-07-18","question":"longest river in tamilnadu","viewed":false,"viewed_date":""},{"_id":"8be97b2faf152ffaf8dc163aaf903780","_rev":"1-2aa210c02d6459c99dfb60818065ff9e","answer":"","answered":false,"answered_by":{"teacher_id":"th-2","teacher_name":"willson, ng"},"answered_date":"","asked_by":{"student_id":"st-1","student_name":"will, smith"},"asked_date":"2020-07-18","question":"longest river in tamilnadu","viewed":false,"viewed_date":""},{"_id":"9265102ade5d79dd03064d757f1a01cf","_rev":"1-46a03f0a52ddc49c050faef59ab3a96b","answer":"","answered":false,"answered_by":{"teacher_id":"th-2","teacher_name":"willson, ng"},"answered_date":"","asked_by":{"student_id":"st-1","student_name":"will, smith"},"asked_date":"2020-07-17","question":"what is blood?","viewed":false,"viewed_date":""},{"_id":"b7989f695585a4cf0fe8d6735df544db","_rev":"1-6186171f22714edd4d2b08fd7042509d","answer":"","answered":false,"answered_by":{"teacher_id":"th-2","teacher_name":"willson, ng"},"answered_date":"","asked_by":{"student_id":"st-1","student_name":"will, smith"},"asked_date":"2020-07-17","question":"What is brain?","viewed":false,"viewed_date":""},{"_id":"b802c0cd0e620f6c718c4568aec9c76f","_rev":"1-091e3ead5b52b1ac4bf69f5a9d6321b4","answer":"","answered":false,"answered_by":{"teacher_id":"th-2","teacher_name":"willson, ng"},"answered_date":"","asked_by":{"student_id":"st-1","student_name":"will, smith"},"asked_date":"2020-07-18","question":"what is the function of lung?","viewed":false,"viewed_date":""},{"_id":"c3e339885a3aeed6ed0748f41f4c71e1","_rev":"1-2aa210c02d6459c99dfb60818065ff9e","answer":"","answered":false,"answered_by":{"teacher_id":"th-2","teacher_name":"willson, ng"},"answered_date":"","asked_by":{"student_id":"st-1","student_name":"will, smith"},"asked_date":"2020-07-18","question":"longest river in tamilnadu","viewed":false,"viewed_date":""},{"_id":"dc675d5b876fbbda11233fb54b554bcd","_rev":"1-55cbfb044b2672aeb124d7ceeebf1ba1","answer":"","answered":false,"answered_by":{"teacher_id":"th-2","teacher_name":"willson, ng"},"answered_date":"","asked_by":{"student_id":"st-1","student_name":"will, smith"},"asked_date":"2020-07-16","question":"How many bone in human body?","viewed":false,"viewed_date":""},{"_id":"ff5f75bada94700f5d8440ede3b84bea","_rev":"1-2aa210c02d6459c99dfb60818065ff9e","answer":"","answered":false,"answered_by":{"teacher_id":"th-2","teacher_name":"willson, ng"},"answered_date":"","asked_by":{"student_id":"st-1","student_name":"will, smith"},"asked_date":"2020-07-18","question":"longest river in tamilnadu","viewed":false,"viewed_date":""},{"_id":"ffa65b4701a6cfa3e66d5b9f8cab0865","_rev":"1-473415527d627eb9832e07d73b1fb787","answer":"","answered":false,"answered_by":{"teacher_id":"th-2","teacher_name":"willson, ng"},"answered_date":"","asked_by":{"student_id":"st-1","student_name":"will, smith"},"asked_date":"2020-07-12","question":"Which state in US has the most number of rivers?","viewed":false,"viewed_date":""}],"success":true}
